David Jay

San Antonio, Texas, United States



djay8400@gmail.com



(210) 209-0264



linkedin.com/in/david-jay-06911a217



https://djay8400.github.io/david-jay-portfolio/

Summary

I have 6 months experience as a Full Stack Web Developer and have provided links to my portfolio of work projects. Before deciding to enter a career in coding, I owned and operated a small Residential inspection business since 2014, but with the recent events of 2020, business slowed down and I decided to pursue my life long dreams of working in coding.

Experience



Full Stack Web Developer

Freelance

Sep 2021 - Present (5 months +)



Inspector

Self-employed

Feb 2014 - Jul 2021 (7 years 6 months)

I built this company from the ground up and managed as many as 6 employees that ran the office and performed the inspections. I managed and trained the inspectors and HR. I created and implemented marketing strategies to gain new customers and led the overall business to completing over 1000 inspections.

Education



The University of Texas at San Antonio

Full Stack Web Developer Coding Bootcamp Certification, Computer Science Jul 2021 - Jan 2022

Licenses & Certifications



UTSA Full Stack Web Developer Certification - The University of Texas at San

Antonio

Skills

Customer-focused Service • Technology Solutions • Project Management • JavaScript • Node.js • Bootstrap • MySQL • React.js • NoSQL • MERN Stack